wellsphere.com 2016-06-18

# Remedy Health Media, LLC

                          This Privacy Policy was last modified and is effective as of August 5, 2014
                                          Remedy Health Media, LLC
                                                     Privacy Policy
Remedy Health Media, LLC (“RHM”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) operates the following list of healthcare and
fitness-related websites: www.remedyhealthmedia.com, www.healthcentral.com, www.intelecare.com,
www.thebody.com, www.thebodypro.com, www.healthcommunities.com, www.mood247.com,
www.healthcommunitiesproviderservices.com, and www.berkeleywellness.com (individually, a “Site”;
collectively, the “Sites”). This is the official Privacy Policy for the Sites. This Privacy Policy forms a part of
your legal agreement with us, along with our Terms of Use and any other Additional Terms.
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY AS IT DESCRIBES HOW WE COLLECT AND USE
INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU ONLINE AND UNDER WHAT CIRCUMSTANCES WE SHARE
INFORMATION ABOUT YOU. Any terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are shall have the meaning
ascribed to them in the Terms of Use.
1.       CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, add or
delete provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time. When we make material changes to this Privacy
Policy, we will inform you by either emailing you or posting a notice on the page from which you access
this Privacy Policy. We display the effective date of this Privacy Policy at the top of this page. Your use of
any of our Sites after the effective date of any such modification, means you accept and agree to be
bound by the Privacy Policy, as modified. You should come back to this web page and review this Privacy
Policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you.
2.       NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW COLLECTED. When you access or visit
any of our Sites, we and our operational service providers (as defined in the “Disclosure to Third Parties”
section below) and others who host our Sites often use “cookies” and other technologies that may
recognize, collect and/or transmit information that is associated with you or your device. These various
technologies may recognize, collect and/or transmit information about your visits to our Sites, such as
your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, the Internet or web domain that referred you, the type of
operating system and browser you are using, the date and time of your visit, data relating to activities
on our Sites (e.g., so-called “clickstream” data) and other technological attributes about your visit to the
Sites. We may use this information to analyze trends, administer the Sites, track user movements on the
Sites and gather aggregate demographic information about visitors so we can continually improve our
Sites.
Cookies and other technologies may also allow our Sites to recognize your computer or device each time
it is used to visit a particular Site, track how you use our Sites, your preferences for features and
functions and, for our Sites that have registration or similar features, they can store information such as
your user name and password so you don’t have to re-enter them each time you return to visit. Most
Internet browsers allow you to delete or disable cookies by changing the settings on your Internet
browser. However, please note, deleting or disabling cookies may affect your ability to use certain
features and functions of our Sites and it may also require you to re-enter certain information each time
you visit or attempt to use our Sites. You should consult the operating instructions that apply to your
browser to determine how to best configure your browser settings for your needs.
3.       PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED. The term “Personal Information” refers to any
information you provide in connection with your use of any of our Sites by which you can be personally

identified. Personal Information may include such things as your name, mobile phone number, street
address, telephone number, date of birth, e-mail address, photographs of yourself, and any other
information which might reasonably be used to identify you. On some of our Sites, we may also collect
Personal Information related to your health, for example, whether you have high blood pressure or
what type of medicine you are taking.
We obtain Personal Information from you when you voluntarily submit it to us (or our operational
service providers) or provide it on one or more of our Sites in order to allow you to register, subscribe or
take advantage of certain features, functions, services, activities, promotions (e.g., sweepstakes and
contests), and content on our Sites (these are referred to as “Content” in our Terms of Use).. For
example, on some of our Sites, we may collect Personal Information that you post within the
community-based features, such as the “Share Your Story” or “Ask a Question” features on the Health
Central site and the “Connect” and “Ask the Experts” features on The Body site. Please note that you
may not be able to use some Content if you choose not to provide your Personal Information when
requested. If you provide or submit your Personal Information to any of our Sites, our policy is to give
you the right to review, update and/or delete your Personal Information, subject to our obligations to
comply with legal, regulatory or internal audit and record-keeping requirements.
4.       HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS USED. We may use the information that we obtain from you,
including Personal Information and information in the aggregate form: (a) to provide you with the
information you have requested (e.g., emailing you health alerts) or to provide you with the services you
have requested (e.g., sending you newsletters; sending you text messages; responding to your request
for a consultation); (b) to improve the Content, appearance and utility of our Sites; (c) to tailor your
experience on our Sites; (d) to track our visitors’ use of our Sites for internal research purposes; (e) to
monitor compliance with our Terms of Use; (f) to notify our visitors of updates to our Sites; (g) to send
you promotional and marketing materials; and (h) for our internal or our business partners’ research
and analysis purposes. If we or any of our Sites collect, maintain, use or intend to share your Personal
Information for purposes other than as described in this Privacy Policy, we will ensure that it is included
within the Additional Terms that applies to the Site or Sites involved or will post a notice to you before
you submit your Personal Information.
5.       PUBLIC POSTINGS. Some of our Sites may permit you to make Postings (as defined in our Terms
of Use). If you make a Posting to any area of a Site that that may be accessed by other users (such as
health-related information you place on a message board, public profile, or chat room), please keep in
mind that such information can be viewed and used by anyone who uses or accesses the Site. Please do
not disclose Personal Information in these areas. Any information you disclose may be used by third
parties we do not control. We are not responsible for any information, including Personal Information,
you choose to disclose to public areas of our Sites, or for any related losses or damages, whether alleged
or actual.
6.       CHILDREN. Our Sites are not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly
solicit or collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian
of a child under the age of 13 and believe he or she has provided Personal Information to us please
notify us at privacy@remedyhealthmedia.com. If you are 13 or older but still a minor in the state in
which you reside (typically 18), you must obtain the consent of your parent or guardian before using our
Sites.
7.       THIRD PARTY LINKS. Our Sites may contain or display information from co-sponsors,
advertisers, retailers, social networks, operational service providers or other unaffiliated third parties
                                                      -2-

(each, a “Third Party”) that offer to make information, goods or services available, provide opportunities
to participate in promotions or engage in activities or that link or redirect your browser to other
websites, materials or organizations. We are not responsible for the privacy practices at these external
websites or their use of your information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms
and conditions for these web sites. If you have any questions regarding the information gathering or
dissemination activities of other web sites, you should consult the privacy policies and terms and
conditions contained on those web sites.
8.       DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES. Our policy is to not sell, rent, lease, provide or otherwise
disclose your Personal Information to unaffiliated entities unless specifically here or in any other terms
that may apply to your use of a particular Site.
We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information to any Third Party we engage for the
purpose of administering, operating, configuring site design, maintaining and providing internal support
for our Sites and Content on the Sites. These Third Parties are called “operational service providers” and
provide internal support to operations and activities and for Site design, development, hosting and
operations. For example, we may employ operational service providers to send direct emails on our
behalf or to provide information technology support. We may also use operational service providers to
display or serve advertising on our Sites, running promotions, as well as for distributing online, email,
messages or web-based newsletters and other information. We take reasonable efforts to ensure that
our operational service providers protect your privacy, and that they are not permitted to use your
Personal Information for their own marketing or promotional purposes.
We also reserve the right to make your Personal Information available to Third Parties in the following
situations:
                when compelled by a governmental agency, law, regulation, a court or other legal
                 process;
                if we believe you are, have or may violate any law, regulation, or our Terms of Use;
                to enforce our Terms of Use or any other agreements we may have with you;
                if we believe you are or may be a threat to the safety, property, interests or rights of
                 RHM or others;
                in order to investigate, respond to or resolve problems or inquiries or defend our
                 interests;
                in a merger, acquisition, change of control, joint venture or other business combination;
                when you otherwise consent.
9.       AGGREGATE OR ANONYMIZED DATA. RHM may, either by itself or in coordination with its
business partners and RHM operational service providers, create aggregate or anonymized data sets
from the Personal Information that we collect. As a general matter, aggregate and anonymized data
sets do not include your Personal Information and cannot be used to identify you. We may disclose such
aggregate or anonymized data sets with our business partners; for example, our business partners may
use such aggregate or anonymized data sets in order to conduct research and analysis.
10.      REMOVAL OR DELETION OF YOUR INFORMATION/OPTING OUT. In general, at your request,
RHM will remove or delete Personal Information that you have provided to us. You may do so by
emailing privacy@remedyhealthmedia.com with your opt-out request. Some of our Sites may permit
you to opt-out of certain Voluntary Communications (as defined in our Terms of Use) for which you have
                                                    -3-

registered or subscribed to receive (e.g., newsletters) and promotional Automatic Communications (as
defined in our Terms of Use). Users may unsubscribe from receiving Voluntary Communications and
promotional Automatic Communications from us at any time by following the instructions contained at
the end of every email.
Please note that you may continue to receive emails from us for up to ten (10) days following your
unsubscribing.
11.      SECURITY. We maintain a reasonable standard of security and try to limit information access to
individuals who need to have such access to perform their responsibilities associated with our Sites and
the Content on our Sites. Despite these efforts, no system can ever be 100% secure. As a result, we
cannot guarantee that the Personal Information stored on our servers will be free from unauthorized
access. By using our Sites you are agreeing to assume this risk and any and all responsibility and liability
that may arise.
12.      CORRECTING OR UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. If you have provided your
Personal Information to us, you can update or delete it by logging into your account or contacting us at
privacy@remedyhealthmedia.com. Although we may provide you with the ability to update or delete
Personal Information directly on our Site, some Personal Information may not be changed or deleted by
you and may require you to contact RHM for verification.
13.      YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS. California Civil Code Section 1798.83, allows individuals
who have provided their Personal Information to us to request information about our disclosures of
certain categories of Personal Information (if any) to third parties for their direct marketing purposes
during the immediately preceding year. If applicable, you may request such information by either
sending an email to our designated Privacy Administrator at privacy@remedyhealthmedia.com or
contacting us via postal mail, proper postage prepaid, at:
Privacy Administrator
Remedy Health Media, LLC
750 Third Avenue, 6th Floor
New York, NY 10017
Attn: Your California Privacy Rights
In addition, under California law, website operators are required to disclose how they respond to web
browser “do not track” signals or other similar mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to
exercise choice regarding the collection of personal information of a consumer over time and across
third party websites, to the extent the operator engages in that collection. At this time, we do not track
our users’ Personal Information over time and across third-party websites. This law also requires
website operators to disclose whether third parties may collect personal information about their users’
online activities over time and across different sites when the users use the operator’s website. We do
not knowingly permit third parties to collect Personal Information about an individual user’s online
activities over time and across different web sites when using our Sites.
14.      CONTACT US. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
privacy@remedyhealthmedia.com.
© 2014 Remedy Health Media, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
                                                     -4-
